oneriot.com 2011-08-23

# Privacy Policy - OneRiot

Last updated: March 18, 2011

At OneRiot, we care a lot about your privacy. It’s important to us that you understand exactly how OneRiot operates its services and how that might relate to your privacy. This privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) applies to all of our web sites, products and services. The purpose of this privacy policy is to give consumers comprehensive information about the information we collect and how we use that information.

### About Our Online Advertising Services

OneRiot works with content and application providers, advertisers, ad networks and other businesses to deliver targeted or personalized ads, to consumers. We target ads using signals such as influence, interest profiles, demographics and realtime conversations. We believe that consumers benefit from receiving more relevant ads and advertisers and publishers benefit from more effective advertising.

### What information do we collect?

OneRiot does not collect information directly from individuals but rather receives information from our partner’s mobile applications and third party service providers. In this light, OneRiot relies on our partners and these third party service providers to inform their users about the purposes for which it collects and uses their personal information.

In order to provide a full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

  * **Twitter information** – we obtain publicly available Twitter information from our partners and third party service providers such as user name, display name, profile information and Tweets.
  * **Mobile device information** – we may automatically receive from our partners information indentifying the user’s location and service provider information garnered via the IP address used to access the mobile Internet or other means, device identifiers, the type of phone or other mobile device used (e.g., iPhone, Blackberry 8800 etc.), the date and time of a user’s mobile internet session, whether one of the mobile ads we facilitate was delivered and, if applicable, a record if that ad was "clicked."
  * **Ad tags** \- we use “pixel tags" and/or similar technologies in our communications to enable us to evaluate when and if advertisements are viewable on the mobile device. A pixel tag is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located within the advertising creative, which is retrieved from a remote site on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual's viewing or receipt of a Web page or message.

### Personally Identifiable Information

Some of the information users choose to share publicly through Twitter may be personally identifiable. We do not send Twitter data we receive from our partners and third party service providers to anyone outside of OneRiot.

### What do we do with the information?

We process collected information for the following purposes:

  * Analyze usage trends and patterns to understand user behavior, improve our services, and optimize advertising for our business partners.
  * Create audience segments and demographic, geographic and interest categories to deliver targeted advertising.
  * Give our clients more information about the performance of their advertising campaigns and improve performance over time.
  * Ensure the technical functioning of our network.
  * Develop new services.

### Opting Out

You can opt-out from us sending you targeted ads by sending an email to [support@oneriot.com](mailto:support@oneriot.com) and including your Twitter ID. Once you opt out, you may continue to receive ads from us, however, they will be based on generic factors, as opposed to data collected and processed in connection with your Twitter ID.

### Disclosure of Your Data

We do not trade, rent or share the personal data we collect with third parties, unless you ask or authorize us to do so.

Although we currently do not have a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, “Affiliates”), we may in the future. We may share some or all of the personal data we collect with these Affiliates, in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

In the event OneRiot goes through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, the personal data we collect will likely be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of OneRiot or its assets may continue to use the personal data we collect as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

### Information Security

OneRiot takes commercially reasonable security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of the personal data we collect and store. These security measures include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store the personal data we collect.

We restrict access to personal information only to OneRiot employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information to operate, develop or improve our Services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations. However, no security system can be fully secured; accordingly, OneRiot cannot guarantee the security of any information you provide to us in connection with the delivery of our services.

### Privacy of Minors

We do not intentionally collect or maintain personal information from those who are under 13 years old.

### Changes to This Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep any prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

### Still Have Questions?

If you have additional questions, please feel free to contact us at: [support@oneriot.com](mailto:support@oneriot.com).
